《指定幸存者》前情提要
Previously on "Designated Survivor"...
国会大厦受到袭击  总统死了
Capitol's been attacked. Eagle is gone.
-整个国会  内阁  -天啊
- Congress, the Cabinet. - Oh, oh, my God.
先生  你现在是美国总统了
Sir, you are now the President.
今晚有些坏人做了一些坏事
Some bad people did something bad tonight,
老爸的职责就是确保我们都安全
and it's Dad's job to make sure we're all safe.
我跟国务卿柯克曼的手下一起工作三年了
I've been with Secretary Kirkman's staff for three years.
现在是柯克曼总统了  而且你并没得到授权
It's President Kirkman now, and you're not authorized.
知不知道始作俑者是谁
Do we know - who's responsible for this?
现在下定论还为时尚早
Still too early to determine.
我们得给大家一个交代
We got to give them something,
现在全世界都在关注我们
the whole world is watching.
我们现在让住房和城市发展部长
We have a Housing and Urban Development Secretary
掌管着美国
running the free world.
你说的可是除掉在位总统
You're talking about removing a sitting president.
我们这里有发现
We got something over here!
慢点
Easy.
能看到什么
What do you see?
没事了  是颗哑弹
It's clear. Bomb's a dud.
没完事之前  不会居功吧
You don't take credit for something until you're done, right?
也许他们才刚刚开始呢
So, what if - they're just getting started?
没有消息
There was no chatter.
汉娜  我知道没有消息
Hannah, I understand there was no chatter,
但我们仍需要核查所有可能的嫌犯
but we still need to check all of the usual suspects --
基地组织  真主党  艾尔萨卡
Al Qaeda, Hezbollah, Al-Sakar.
配合我们的当地执法机关呢
Where are we with local law enforcement?
我已经联系了特区警局
I've coordinated with D.C. Police,
特情局  市局  国会大厦
Secret Service, Metro, and Capitol.
好  干得好
All right, that's good.
要记住  重要人物名单
Now, remember -- - The high-value target list
从白宫开始排
only starts with the White House.
我们得加强所有位置的安保措施
We need to heighten security at every location.
已经加强了
Already taken care of.
来处理这个炸弹
Hey! Let's get on this bomb!
-你要带去给安德鲁斯吗  -对
- You taking that bomb to Andrews? - Yeah.
高层要求所有东西全部登记在案
Top brass wants everything cataloged under one roof.
副局长  请过来一下
Deputy Director! We need you over here!
好
All right.
好的  拉出来
All right, pull that out!
美国民众们
My fellow Americans,
今晚  我们遭遇了恐怖袭击
tonight our way of life came under attack.
早间新闻  柯克曼总统发表第一次讲话
不法分子试图用这种怯懦的行为削弱我们
This act of cowardice was meant to cripple our nation.
但一如以往  美国将向全世界展示
But as before, America will show the world
我们不会被恐惧压垮
that we will not bow down to fear,
我们将狠狠还击  坚定地走下去
that we will fight back, that we will persevere.
这是汤姆·柯克曼总统第一次对全国发表讲话
And this was President Tom Kirkman's first address to the nation.
就在两小时前  他才匆匆宣誓就任总统一职
It came just two hours after he was unceremoniously sworn in as our new president.
早间新闻  柯克曼总统的第一次讲话
不幸的是  昨晚的讲话
Unfortunately, last night's speech
并没有缓和公众紧绷的神经
did little to calm the frayed nerves...
不说演讲内容
Words aside,
柯克曼之前是住房和城市发展部长  未经选举
Kirkman is an unelected, untested HUD secretary
柯克曼是正确的人选吗
而如今全世界都需要领导力
at a time where the world is looking for leadership.
国会大厦的遗骸...
...remains of the Capitol,
全力搜救幸存者
searching for both survivors
国会山的搜索仍在继续
为全国人民都关注的问题
and answers to the questions
找到答案
all Americans are asking --
怎么会这样
How did this happen
我们还安全吗...
and will life ever be the sa--
-早安  总统先生  -早上好
- Morning, Mr. President. - Good morning.
西侧  在右边还是左边
West Wing, right or left?
这边走  在右手边  总统先生
This way, to the right, sir.
谢谢
Thank you very much.
凤凰[总统]出发了
Phoenix on the move.
早上好  总统先生
Good morning, sir.
我妻子今天不想让我来
My wife didn't want me to come in today.
她担心白宫就是下一个目标
She's afraid the White House is next.
我昨晚本该过去的
I was supposed to go last night,
但我没找到保姆就没去
but I couldn't get a sitter.
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
头条新闻  国会大厦致命爆炸案
梅丽莎死了  大家都死了
Melissa's dead, everyone's dead.
总统先生
Mr. President.
-亚伦  -早上好
- Aaron. - Good morning.
-大家在总统办公室等着向您汇报  -好
- We have a briefing waiting for you in the Oval, sir. - Good.
-总统先生  -怀特  对吗
- Mr. President. - Wyatt, right?
-是的  先生  -谢谢
- Yes, sir. - Thank you.
总统先生  我提醒一下您
Sir, I just have to warn you.
这里可能会比您之前更加紧张和忙碌
This might be a bit more hectic than you're used to.
我明白  应该能搞定
I-I understand. I think we'll be fine.
我们已经加强了油气管道
We've added increased security to our oil and gas pipelines,
电网  炼油厂  化工储罐的安全戒备
power grids, refineries, chemical storage tanks.
公众交通依然要保持关闭
Mass transit is still on lock down --
飞机  火车等等
planes and trains.
仍然要禁止外来移民
Immigration remains frozen.
总统先生  请您授权
Sir, you have to authorize
-我们立即关闭银行  -不  不能关银行
- we close the banks immediately. - No, we can't do that.
我们不能阻止民众支取自己的财产
We cannot keep the American people from their money.
48小时取不了钱
48 hours without Bank of America
总比48个月经济萧条强
is better than a 48-month depression.
如果所有人都同时提款
If everyone withdraws their money at the same time,
银行会破产
the banks will collapse.
炸弹的事调查得怎样了
Where are we at with the bombing?
亚特伍德副局长很快会来汇报
Deputy Director Atwood will be briefing us soon,
我们排查了有能力和资金制造此次爆炸案的组织
but we're looking at groups with the skills and resources to do something like this.
黎巴嫩真主党  基地组织  朝鲜  三原党
Hezbollah, Al-Qaeda, North Korea, RGB.
密歇根州的暴力事件是怎么回事
Well, what's this about violence in Michigan?
我们收到报告  迪尔伯恩市发生突发事件
We're getting reports of flare-ups in Dearborn.
警方认为是当地的穆斯林群体所为
Police targeting the local Muslim community.
但我想知道的是
Yeah, but what I want to know is
恐怖分子是如何将爆炸物
how did the terrorists bring explosives
成功带进国会大厦的
into the Capitol Building in the first place.
我们正在调查
We're working on that.
与此同时  我们要想尽一切办法
In the meantime, we have to go after everyone we suspect.
追踪所有嫌疑人  和他们的家人
We go after them, after their families any way we can.
抱歉  你是在提议动用私刑吗
I'm sorry. Are you talking about enhanced interrogation?
他们毁掉了国会大厦
They destroyed our Capitol.
我们应该采取一切必要措施
I'm saying we do whatever we have to do.
我可以打扰一下吗
Can I just get a moment?
听我说  能不能一次只关注一件事
Everybody, why don't we just focus on one thing at a time?
打扰一下
Please, excuse me.
抱歉  你能让我静一静吗
Please, can you just give me a moment?
住房与城市发展部部长专座
总统专座
第一季
第二集
总统专座
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
最新最快海外影视字幕下载
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译：   石头   长颈鹿   桃子   panglovelai   Luna
■
汤姆  抱歉
Tom... I'm sorry.
总统先生
Mr. President.
我只是想自己静一静
I just needed to find somewhere quiet.
翻译：  吸吸粒呀   喜乐儿   Michael   silence   星星与野狗
确实  那边有点太吵闹了
Yeah, admittedly, it got a little loud in there.
吵闹
Loud?
球赛可以吵闹  亚伦
A Caps game is loud, Aaron.
校对：    青椒     panglovelai
但在总统办公室里  那就是混乱
Back there in the Oval Office, that was chaos.
我们需要秩序和制度  否则将一事无成
We need order, a system, or this is never gonna work.
时间轴：   Avis    姜姜
我们需要让美国政府重新运作起来
We need to get this government up and running.
还要尽快组建内阁
We... We need a cabinet and fast.
后期： 虫虫不咬人     总监： 小早从小爱MQ
好主意  总统先生
That's a good idea, sir,
首要任务是提名您的幕僚长
but first order of business is going to be naming your Chief of Staff.
你认真的吗  这么快就开始玩手段了
Seriously? You're making a play right now?
■
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
够了
Enough!
我还没决定好选谁
I'm not ready to make that decision.
我需要你们两人同心协力
What I need is both of you to step up
帮助我组建内阁
and help me put together a cabinet.
能做到吗
Tell me you can do that.
-可以  总统先生  -当然
- Yes, Mr. President. - Of course.
很好
Good.
我们要暂时关闭银行
For now, we're gonna close the banks.
但自动提款机和信用卡依然能用
ATMs and credit will still be available.
我要你们严密监控密歇根州的局势
I want you to monitor the situation in Michigan,
还要加快爆炸事件的调查进度
and I want you to keep me up to speed
并且及时向我汇报
on the investigation into the bombing.
全国人民都想知道是谁干的
The American people want to know who did this,
-我也是  -知道了
- and so do I. - Sir.
还有
Also...
稍后我要去察看国会大厦
Later today, I want to see the Capitol Building,
国会大厦遗址
or what's left of it.
您确定要在这个节骨眼去吗  先生
Are you sure that's a... good idea right now, sir?
不  您就应该现在去  总统先生
No, no, no. Th--that -- that's exactly what you need, sir.
再次公关
A do-over.
昨晚的演讲没有缓解国民的紧张情绪
L-Last night's speech didn't exactly put minds at ease.
但总统亲自去现场
But you, sir, at the site...
可以传达一个信息
now that sends a message.
-表现出...  -默哀  亚伦
- It shows a... - Respect, Aaron.
我是为了默哀
it shows respect.
不是在做秀
It's not a photo-op.
-听您安排  先生  -很好
- Whatever you say, sir. - Good.
回去工作吧
Let's get back to work.
政府大楼成为废墟
先生  站着别动
Sir. Hold it right there.
早上好  怎么了吗
Morning, what's going on?
-背包里装的是什么  -什么
- What's in the backpack? - What?
你的背包里装着什么
Your backpack... what's in it?
只是些工作上的东西
Uh, just my stuff for, uh, work...
-文件之类的  -你在哪里工作
- Papers and stuff. - Where do you work?
我在白宫工作
I work at the White House.
真的吗  在白宫吗
Really? The White House?
是啊  总统休息的地方
Yeah, you know, where the President sleeps.
少来这一套
You being a wise ass?
我想知道为什么你们要拦我
I'd like to know why you stopped me.
你还是先上报住址  拿出身份证来吧
Why don't you tell us where you live and show us some I.D. First.
我就住在那里
I live right there.
又冷又窄
It's cold and it's cramped,
但是可以走路去健身房
but I can walk to my gym,
所以也还不错
so I got that going for me.
赛斯·怀特
Seth Wright.
是你的真名吗
Is that your real name?
我妈妈是这么说的
According to my mother.
基斯
Keith.
他的身份没问题
This looks good.
感谢合作  怀特先生
Thanks for your cooperation, Mr. Wright.
谢谢你
Thank you.
注意安全
Yeah, stay safe.
我得挂了
Look, I got to go.
告诉妈妈我爱她
Tell Mom I love her.
内阁成员候选人
Okay, cabinet members.
布兰查德怎么样
What about Blanchard?
当州议员吗
For State?
他任副职三年
He's qualified-- three years as deputy.
他还有两个私密的脸书账号
He also has two secret Facebook accounts
并且对照看他小孩的女孩子们颇有兴趣
and an affinity for the coeds who look after his kids.
我觉得加菲尔德合适
I'm thinking Garfield's our guy.
不行  再想想
No, think again.
他在国会山树敌太多
He's made more than a few enemies on the Hill.
艾米丽  我不想打击你
Emily, I hate to break it to you,
但国会山已经不在了
but there is no Hill anymore.
天哪
Oh, my God.
国会山已经不在了
There's no Hill anymore.
密歇根出事了
Something happened in Michigan.
什么
What?
总统先生
Mr. President.
你不必一看见我就起身敬礼
You don't need to get up every time I walk into a room.
我又不是女王
I'm not the Queen.
确实  您一点也不像
No, sir. Virtually no resemblance.
很抱歉打扰你
I'm sorry to interrupt.
我...我其实是来道歉的
I-- I actually came in to apologize.
为何道歉
Apologize?
昨晚你为我写了一篇非常棒的演讲稿
Last night, you wrote me a home run of a speech.
但今天早上
This morning,
新闻界似乎更希望让其他人来念
it seems like the press wished anybody else delivered it but me.
总统先生
Mr. President.
也许国民只是还没有准备好
Maybe the country's just not ready, yet,
去齐心协力拥护谁
to come together behind anyone,
哪怕你有着世界一流的演讲稿
even with the best speech in the world.
也许吧
Maybe.
总统先生
Mr. President.
有事情需要跟您汇报
There's something you need to see.
警方在穆斯林社区
Police imposing a curfew
特大事件  密歇根州迪尔伯恩市  全城宵禁
大肆实施宵禁
on predominantly Muslim neighborhoods
并勒令居民必须服从  否则将被拘捕
and ordering residents to obey it or face arrest.
这些公民
These are citizens
并未受到任何犯罪指控
who have not been charged with any crimes,
只因为信仰就遭遇如此对待
who are simply targeted because of their religious beliefs.
美国公民自由联盟
The American Civil Liberties Union
公开谴责迪尔伯恩警方的这一行为
denounced the actions by Dearborn police
-侵害了...  -总统先生  准备好了
- as a violation of an individual's... - Mr. President, we're ready.
公民基本权利
...basic civil rights.
但考虑到国会大厦遭遇了恐怖袭击
But in the wake of the attack on the Capitol,
有人说这才是我国急需的监管方式
some are saying this is just the type of policing this country needs.
-州长叫什么  -罗伊斯
- Governor...? - Royce.
罗伊斯州长  你好吗
Governor Royce, how are you?
差不多吧
Uh, about as expected.
你可以想象  很多事情需要整顿
There's a lot to manage here, as you can imagine.
我知道  我想帮助你
I know, and I want to help.
我看了新闻  迪尔伯恩的警察
I've seen reports - that the police in Dearborn
正在围捕穆斯林社区的居民
are rounding up members of the Muslim community.
多谢好意  我知道这件事
Thank you, sir. Yes, I'm aware.
我可以帮你制止那些警察
Well, like I said, we'd like to help you stop the police.
为什么要制止他们
Why would I stop the police?
他们是在执行我的命令
They're acting on my orders.
-你的命令  -没错
- Your orders? - That's correct.
我不知道你是否了解
I don't know if you know this,
我这里是穆斯林人口最多的市
but I have the largest Muslim population in the country, here.
这并不代表他们就会犯法
That doesn't mean they're doing anything wrong
就会变成激进分子
or that they've been radicalized.
对  但我敢肯定他们知道内情
No, but I'm willing to bet they know someone who is.
州长  你不能因为单纯的恐惧
Governor, you can't target an innocent population
就伤害无辜大众
because you're scared.
-你有责任  -我对所有公民都有责任
- You have a responsibility-- - To all my citizens.
我的首要职责是保障他们的安全
And my first and only priority is to make sure they're safe,
而这一点
something that Washington--
华盛顿  或者说曾经的政府
if-- if there even is such a place anymore--
似乎并没有做到
has proven incapable of doing.
州长  联邦政府...
Governor, the federal government--
昨晚被彻底击垮了
...Was effectively snuffed out last night.
国会没了  最高法院也没了
There is no Congress, there is no Supreme Court.
在密歇根公民的问题上
When it comes to the people of Michigan,
我是最高权威
I am the highest authority,
你无权命令我
and you have none over me.
恕我直言  我现在是国家总统
With all due respect, sir, I am the President.
我不认
Not mine.
无需跟我浪费口舌了  柯克曼先生
so you'll have to excuse me, Mr. Kirkman.
你先慢慢学习如何当总统
While you're busy learning how to become President,
我还有一千万公民要保护
I've got 10 million citizens to protect.
州长
Governor?
罗伊斯州长  听得到吗
Governor Royce? Hello?
先生  知道世界各国元首
Sir, you should know that messages of support
都在接连不断发来支持贺电
continue to pour in from heads of state around the world.
我们应该看看哪些需要由您亲自回复
We should go over which calls you want to return personally.
全部都亲自回吧
I would think all of them.
大概有多少来电
How many calls are we talking about?
一共175通  先生
About 175, sir.
那还是排下先后顺序吧
Maybe we should prioritize.
总统先生
Mr. President.
我想跟您说
I want you to know that I don't care
我不在意那些所谓的专家们怎么说
what the so-called pundits are saying.
您昨晚的发言让我十分感动
I was very moved by your words last night.
谢谢你
Well, thank you.
不好意思  请问你是谁
Excuse me, but who are you?
总统先生  这是女议员金布尔·霍斯拉滕
Mr. President, this is congresswoman Kimble Hookstraten.
女议员
Congresswoman.
我是另一位指定幸存者
Yes, I was last night's other designated survivor.
另一位...
Other designated...
请借一步说话
Excuse us, please.
谢谢你
Thank you, sir.
有两个指定幸存者吗
There are - two designated survivors?
是的  共和党也选出了
Yeah, the Republicans chose someone
一位发表国情咨文演说的人
to sit out of - the State of the Union, as well.
为了保障他们的权益
So they'd be represented.
聪明
Smart.
你知道多少关于霍斯拉滕的事
Hey, what do you know about Hookstraten?
你曾经就职于参议员凯雷旗下
Um, you were - on Senator Carlyle's staff
他们都在众议院筹款委员会  对吧
when they were both on Ways and Means, weren't you?
-跟踪狂  -说正经的
- Stalker. - Come on.
她很聪明  非常聪明
She's smart. Very smart.
第三代华盛顿特区贵族
Third-generation D.C. blue blood,
从政九年  共和党纪律委员
nine years, Republican whip,
对政坛所有人都了如指掌
knows every detail about every player in town.
也就是说  她比现任总统有经验得多
So you're saying - she's a lot more experienced than the President?
走吧  我们去给罗伊斯州长打电话
Come on. Let's go get Governor Royce on the phone.
435名代表  100名参议员和9名法官
435 representatives, 100 senators, and 9 justices.
现在只剩下我们两个了
And now it's just down to the two of us.
我理解  都不知道该悔恨
I know. You don't know whether to feel...
还是该庆幸自己活了下来
ashamed or grateful to be alive.
我想道歉
Apologetic.
您说什么
Sir?
向被迫接受我作为领导人的美国公民道歉
To the American people for being stuck with me as their leader.
直面现实吧  专家们说得很有道理
I mean, let's face it. The pundits might be right.
总统先生
Mr. President.
您知道我今天早上做了什么吗
Do you know what I did this morning, sir?
我哭泣并祈祷了
I cried and then I prayed.
你知道我上次这样是什么时候吗
Do you know when the last time I did those two things together was?
9.11的时候
9.11?
那时候没人认为我们能挺过来
Nobody thought we could get through it back then,
但是我们做到了
but we did.
现在也没人认为我们能坚持下去
And nobody thinks - we can get through it now,
但我们会的
but we will.
现在白宫属于你
This is your house now.
尽情发挥你的才能
So make it your own.
你需要什么  尽管提出来
Whatever you need, just ask.
共和党  民主党还是无党派人士
Republican, Democrat, Independent
都不重要了
it doesn't matter anymore.
今天我们都是美国人
We're all Americans today.
谢谢你  女议员
Thank you, congresswoman.
请叫我金布尔
Kimble, please.
好的
Okay.
金布尔  今天下午晚些时候
Kimble, later this afternoon,
我要去国会现场感谢急救先遣队
I'm going to the Capitol site to thank the first responders.
如果我们两个人一起去
I think it would be a nice show of unity
可以让民众看到政府的团结
if we were to do that together.
你觉得怎么样
What do you say?
我很荣幸
I'd be honored, sir.
谢谢您  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
谢谢
Thank you.
罗尼  那是未爆炸的炸弹吗
Ronnie, is that the unexploded munition?
是的
Yep.
有什么进展
What's it telling us?
这是俄罗斯反坦克雷
Russian anti-tank mine,
很可能是从阿富汗战区得到的
likely pulled from the ground in Afghanistan.
但是看这里
But look here.
内核是被拆过的
The guts are cannibalized.
外面是斯拉夫产的
Cyrillic on the outside,
密封环却是巴基斯坦的
but the lock ring is Pakistani,
撞针更加新一点  很可能来自伊朗
and the firing pin is newer, probably Iranian.
这和圣战恐怖组织
Well, that is consistent with what we've seen
手里的地雷是一样的
from some Jihadist terror groups.
拿到其他炸弹的检测结果之后
Well, we should be able to point the finger directly
就应该知道谁是始作俑者了
when we get the lab results from the other bombs.
好的  但是这一枚
Right, but this one,
为什么这一枚没有爆炸
why didn't this one go off?
很多原因
Any number of reasons.
俄罗斯的红线和伊朗的绿线不搭
Russian red wire to Iranian green doesn't work,
主爆炸物降解了
the main charge degraded.
但是也不排除人为原因
But I wouldn't rule out good old-fashioned human error.
难道这些幕后真凶
You're telling me that the people
在一举炸毁美国首都之前
who blew up our U.S. Capitol in one shot,
没有测试触发器和接线吗
didn't test the triggers, the wiring?
你想说什么
Then what are you suggesting?
汉娜
Hannah?
也许这枚炸弹本来就不会爆炸
What if this bomb - wasn't meant to explode?
凶手只是希望我们找到它
What if it was meant to be found?
我不管州长在做什么
Look, I don't care - what the Governor's doing.
美国总统要跟他讲话
The President of the United Sates needs to talk to him.
这不是请求  这是命令
No, I'm not -- I'm not asking you. I'm telling you.
不要让我等
I'm not -- I'm not gonna hold.
该死
Damn it!
万万没想到  有资格担任总检察长的人
You'd think - there would be more people
居然这么少
qualified for Attorney General.
我该说什么好呢
What the hell am I supposed to say?
你是在自言自语吗
Is this a writer thing?
我希望通过柯克曼的现场讲话
I'm trying to find a way to unite us
让美国民众团结起来
at Kirkman's remarks at the rubble,
但密歇根可能只是个开端
but Michigan is probably just the beginning.
世界正在分崩离析
The world is falling apart.
这个就不要写在讲话稿里了
Probably don't want to put that in the speech.
没错  我还在
Yes, I'm still here.
天哪  难以置信
God, it's unbelievable.
温布兰特不错
I like Wynbrandt.
他晚上去上城市学院
He went to city college at night,
读法律系  非常顾家
law school, good family man.
梅西比较合适
Massey's our guy.
他为托马斯工作过  耶鲁毕业
He clerked for Thomas, he went to Yale,
是法律杂志的编辑
editor of the Law Journal.
那只是写在纸上给你看的
It's all about what's on paper for you.
我听过温布兰特讲话
I heard Wynbrandt speak.
他有正确的价值观
The man has good values.
艾米丽  密歇根州州长
Emily, the Governor of Michigan
基本宣称密歇根州要独立了
is basically declaring his state a sovereign nation,
现在没时间讨论价值观
so we don't have time for values.
这个也不能写进讲话里  对吗
I probably shouldn't put that in the speech either, right?
罗伊斯州长这么说的吗
Governor Royce said that?
说他是最高权威
That he's the highest authority?
就是这么说的  而且斩钉截铁
That's what he said -- and in no uncertain terms.
说完就挂了我的电话
Then he hung the phone up on me.
他不能这么做
Well, - he doesn't get to do that.
他有宪法赋予的义务...
He has a constitutional obligation --
你还不明白吗  艾丽克斯
Don't you get it, Alex?
罗伊斯想要撕毁宪法
Royce wants - to tear up the Constitution,
而且不仅是他一个人
and he's not the only one.
你不能让他这么做
Well, you can't let him.
相信我  我不会的
Trust me, I'm not going to.
总检察长办公室的几位律师
We've got some lawyers coming over
已经在过来的路上了
from the Attorney General's office.
我们会弄清楚可以用哪些法律手段
We'll figure out - what our legal options are,
会处理好这件事
and we're handle it.
你怎么样
How you holding up?
我和邓肯联系过了  法院都关闭了
I spoke to Duncan. The courts are closed.
市场  银行  学校  机场  都关闭了
Markets, banks, schools, airports, everything.
公司里一半的初级助理
Half the junior associates in the firm,
都在考虑离开华盛顿
they're thinking of leaving Washington.
佩妮怎么样
How's Penny?
你觉得她能想清楚发生了什么吗
You think she even understands what's happening?
她只知道我们现在住在白宫
Besides the fact that we now live in the White House,
她爸爸成了总统
her father is the President,
还有她睡在一张很大的床上
and she's sleeping in a very big bed,
其余都不明白
no, not really.
我一直努力让她不看电视
I've been trying to keep her away from the TV.
李奥呢
And Leo?
他整天都在房间里  关着门
He's been in his room all day, with the door shut.
基本和他往常一样
So, basically being Leo.
算是吧
Basically.
你觉得我们能不能  就五分钟
Do you think we could, for five minutes,
假装这一切没有发生
just pretend that - this isn't really happening?
在这总统办公室里有点困难啊
Kind of hard to do in the Oval Office.
抱歉  先生  我说了你在忙
I'm sorry, sir. I told him you were busy.
没关系
It's all right.
有什么事  将军
How can I help you, General?
恐怕我们有些事情
I'm afraid that's something
需要私下商量一下  总统先生
we have to discuss in private, Mr. President.
这位是我妻子
Oh. This is my wife.
您的妻子没有最高权限  先生
Your wife does not have code-word clearance, sir.
好的
Of course.
我出去
I'll go.
谢谢夫人
Ma'am.
什么事
What is it?
我和联邦调查局副局长亚特伍德联系了
I just spoke to - FBI Deputy Director Atwood.
实验室鉴定结果出来了
The lab results came in.
他们已经确定了爆炸物的来源
They've made a positive I.D. on the explosives.
我们知道是谁炸了国会大厦
We know - who blew up the Capitol.
艾尔萨卡喜欢大规模伤亡袭击
Al-Sakar likes mass-casuality attacks --
在马尼拉埋下氯气罐
a chlorine storage tank in Manila,
把沙林毒气罐投掷到内罗比军事基地
sarin gas tanks lobbed onto our military base in Nairobi.
联调局爆炸装置中心的初步分析显示
Preliminary analysis from the FBI's Explosive Device Center
在国会大厦废墟发现的碎片
tells us that residue found on the Capitol debris
和艾尔萨卡使用过的炸弹一致
is consistent with bombs used by Al-Sakar in the past.
总统先生
Mr. President,
政府可以公开宣布艾尔萨卡
it's time to publicly name Al-Sakar
是这次犯罪行为的始作俑者
as the perpetrator of this crime
并且采取相应的行动了
and take appropriate action.
在采取任何行动之前
Okay. Before we do anything,
联邦调查局是否确信
the FBI is absolutely certain
是艾尔萨卡制造了这场袭击
that Al-Sakar was behind the attack?
75%确信  先生
75%, sir.
75%吗
75%?
对于这样的任务来说已经很高了
That's as high as it gets when it comes to a call like this.
75%在考试中只能得C  将军
75% is still a "C" On a test, General.
这不是考试  这是战争
This is not a test. This is war.
那就更应该查得准确一些  不是吗
All the more reason to get it right, don't you think?
总统先生  我知道我们曾有过摩擦
Sir, I know we got off on the wrong foot.
你昨晚幸运地躲过了伊朗人的袭击
You did a fine job staving off the Iranians last night.
但我提醒你这个国家现在命悬一线
But I am advising you that the country is on the brink,
说话解决不了问题
and talk will not work here.
美国急需行动
America is demanding action
而我现在给了你一个我们要消灭的敌人
and I am giving you an enemy we can kill.
你以为我不想
You think I don't want to strike back
给凶手一记反击吗
against the people who did this?
我失去了同事  朋友  我爱的人
I lost colleagues, friends, people I love.
我要找出从计划到执行
I want to find every single person
这次袭击的每一个人
involved in this attack from planning to execution
将他们碎尸万段
and rip them limb from limb,
所以我得确切地知道到底是谁做的
which is why I need to know exactly who did this.
超过75%再来找我
Come back to me with more than 75%,
到时我亲自发射导弹
and I'll launch the damn missiles myself.
还需要多少
How much more?
25%啊
25%, damn it!
截至三十分钟前
The death toll as of 30 minutes ago
死亡人数超过九百人
is 900 plus.
包括总统  副总统  内阁
That includes the President, Vice President, Cabinet,
已确认身份的
those we've been able to I.D.
国会及最高法院职员
from Congress and the Supreme Court...
联调局局长雅各布也确认死亡
and FBI Director Jacobs is also confirmed dead.
目前推测是艾尔萨卡所为
The working theory is, this is the work of Al-Sakar.
我们知道他们是基地组织最新的分支
So as we know, this is the latest offshoot of Al-Qaeda.
他们散布在整个北非地区
They are dispersed throughout North Africa,
非常难以追踪
which makes them very, very hard to track.
所以我们得随机应变
So we need to be crafty.
我们要调集我们所有的资源
We need to reach out to your sources,
不计成本
spread some cash around,
尽一切努力搜寻线索
do whatever you have to do to firm up that link.
有人宣称负责吗
What about credit?
那是什么
What about it?
艾尔萨卡宣称对此事负责了吗
Is Al-Sakar taking credit?
没有
No, they haven't.
但当年本·拉登过了几个月
But it was months before Bin Laden
才宣称对袭击双子塔的事负责  所以...
took responsibility for the Towers, so...
散会
That's all for now.
威尔士探员
Agent Wells.
你怎么样
How are you doing?
跟别人一样吧
Same as everyone else, I guess.
我刚从安德鲁斯那过来
I just came from Andrews.
我们发现的未引爆爆炸物
The bomb we just found, the UXO,
可能跟你所想的不太一样
it may not be telling you what you think it is.
说来听听
Okay, I'll bite.
好  如果他们就想让我们找到这个呢
All right, well, what if they wanted us to find it
好让我们把注意力集中在艾尔萨卡上
so that we would look at Al-Sakar
忽视其他可能
and not consider any other options.
你的推测有证据支持吗
Can you back up your theory?
09年在伊拉克我的推测很准
Well, my theories were good enough for you in '09 in Iraq.
这不一样  汉娜  你知道的
This is different, Hannah, and you know it.
况且我已经跟科克兰将军
Besides, I've already talked to General Cochrane
和联席会议打过招呼了
and the Joint Chiefs.
但你还是得跟总统报告的吧
But you're still gonna brief the President later, right?
最好把各方推测都说一下  你觉得呢
Best to give them all the theories, don't you think?
那如果不是艾尔萨卡
So if it wasn't Al-Sakar,
是谁炸了国会大厦
who blew up the Capitol Building?
我还不知道  这才是我最害怕的
I don't know yet, and that's what scares me.
谢谢你  麦克
Thanks, Mike.
我要怎么做
Okay, w-what do I do?
我需要微笑吗
Am I supposed to smile
我到时候大概会想哭
because I'll probably feel like crying.
-做你自己就好  -我知道  只是
- Just be yourself. - I know, I just --
我不想让你失望
I don't want to let you down.
我不想让这个国家失望
I don't want to let the country down,
我讨厌他们给我选的这件衣服
and I hate this that they picked it out for me.
你瞧  我就像个白宫里的沙发
Look. I look like the White House sofa.
你里面还要穿这个的  夫人
It's to fit over this, ma'am.
麦克  这些东西有必要吗
Mike, is this all really necessary?
总统及其家人有两种
Two ways the President and his family
离开白宫的方法
can leave the White House --
要么身穿防弹背心
out the front door in Kevlar vests
随13辆装甲车车队从前门出
and a 13-car armored motorcade
要么戴顶棒球帽坐轿车从后门出去
or out the back in a Chevy and a ball cap.
给我衣服
Give me the coat.
爸爸
Daddy!
小豌豆  还好吗
Hey, little pea, how are you?
你穿的是什么
What are you wearing?
这个吗
Oh, this?
这个是怕我摔跤保护我的
This is just to protect me in case I fall down.
厉害的是  你打我我不会痛
Cool thing is you can punch it, and I won't feel a thing.
来试试
Go on, try.
来
Come here.
我很爱你
I love you so much.
-到时间了  -好
- It's time, sir. - Okay.
等等  李奥哪去了
H-H-Hold on. W-Where's Leo?
别紧张  妈  我在这
Relax, Mom, I'm here.
好  你看好你妹妹
Okay, you need to watch your sister.
别让她看电视  好吗
And keep her away from the TV, okay?
新闻太过真实了
Any of the news, it's too real.
她不需要看
She doesn't need to see it.
知道了吗
Have you got that?
我知道了
Yeah, I understand.
先生  你不系领带吗
Sir, you won't be wearing a tie?
这不是正式场合  亚伦
It's not a formal occasion, Aaron.
好的  我们走
Ok. Let's go.
凤凰准备好了正在路上
Phoenix is ready and on the move.
麦克  只是好奇  之前是什么
Mike, just out of curiosity, what was it before?
先生
Sir?
我当住房和城市发展部部长时的代号
My code name when I was Secretary of HUD,
是什么
what was it?
眼镜  长官
"Glasses," Sir.
我们三小时前给州长留言了
We left word for the Governor three hours ago.
好吧  请再和他说一次
Yeah, p-please tell him, again.
别管政界的人了  他们一向粗鲁无礼
Forget politics, it's just plain rude.
人们到底怎么了
I mean, what the hell's wrong with people anyway?
人们很害怕  亚伦
People are scared, Aaron.
国会过去一直是力量的象征
The Capitol used to be a symbol of strength,
现在变成了一堆灰烬
and now it's a pile of ashes.
我们认识的人都不见了
And everyone we know is gone.
你可以想想今天  每一天
You would think today, of all days,
人们至少能够假装是好人
people could at least pretend to be decent human beings.
你为什么这么惊讶
Why are you so surprised?
灾难让人们既感激又害怕
Tragedy either makes people appreciate their fellow men,
他们的同伴
or fear them.
州长也不例外  他只是被选出来的
The Governor's no different. He's just elected.
谢谢你能和我一起来
Thanks for coming with me.
不用谢
Of course.
怎么了
What?
昨天  我还被要求卸任
Yesterday, I was asked to resign,
我们在聊搬去蒙特利尔的事
and we were talking about moving to Montreal.
现在我却在试着让整个美国政府
Now I'm trying to put the entire U.S. Government
凝聚起来
back together
阻止这个国家分裂
and stop the country from tearing itself apart.
地狱般的一天
Hell of a day.
是的
Yeah.
总统的车队来了
That's the President's motorcade coming in.
当心
Look out.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready for this?
怎么可能有人准备好
How can anybody be ready for this?
好吧  专心工作
All right, hold the work. Hold the work.
我的天
My God.
先生
Sir.
总统先生
Mr. President.
汤姆
Tom.
总统先生
Mr. President,
我是杰森·阿特伍德  副局长
I'm Jason Atwood, Deputy Director.
-里面为您准备好了一份简报  先生  -好的
- We got a briefing ready for you inside, sir. - Okay.
恐怖爆炸装置分析中心的初步分析
Prelim analysis from TEDAC
表明残骸上找到的的爆炸残渣
indicates that the explosive residue found on
是黑索今  也被叫做旋风炸药
the debris is called cyclonite, also known as RDX.
我们认为它和塑化剂混合在一起
We believe it was mixed with a plasticizer.
这样能使破坏力达到最大
And that's - what maximizes the destruction,
让房子自己倒塌
allowed the chamber to come down on itself?
确实
Exactly.
艾尔萨卡已经开始使用黑索今了吗
And Al-Sakar has access to RDX?
是的长官  这是他们最拿手的
Yes, sir. It's their signature.
你们找到的装置呢  炸弹
What about the device you found -- the bomb?
它为什么没爆炸
Why didn't it go off?
我们认为是人为失误
We believe it was human error.
我们还在进行一些试验
We're still running some tests.
好的  谢谢  副局长
Okay. Thank you, Deputy Director.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
我们会向您实时通报的
We'll keep you updated.
麦克  拿着我的外套
Mike, take my coat.
先生  我需要您穿上外套
Sir, I'm gonna need you to keep that vest on.
麦克  我们来这是为了建立信心
Mike, we're here to project confidence.
这件外套能够帮你重建信心吗
Does this vest project confidence to you?
谢谢
Thank you.
-我赢了  -你作弊
- I win. - You cheated.
-我知道你的把戏  小姑娘  -我没有
- I know your game, little girl. - I did not.
我接个电话
Oh, I got to take this.
你应该照看我
You're supposed to watch me.
是白宫打来的  佩妮
It's the White House, Penny.
我确定你很安全
I'm sure you're safe.
对于新任总统柯克曼
A truly somber moment,
来说是一个沉重的时刻
as newly sworn-in President Kirkman
他于今日亲临
makes his first visit
了恐怖袭击现场
to the site of the terrorist attack.
我们拭目以待他对公众的解释
We will stand by for his comments to the nation.
好多照相机  亚伦
A lot of cameras, Aaron.
因为您是总统  先生
You are the President, sir.
打扰一下  那个可以借给我吗
Excuse me. Could I borrow that?
给您 先生
Here you go, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
-按这里吗  -是的
- Just press here? - Yeah.
你们好  我叫汤姆·柯克曼
Hello, my name is Tom Kirkman.
大概昨晚十点半
Last night at approximately 10:30 p.m.,
我宣誓就职美国总统
I was sworn in as President of the United States.
我来这里
I've come down here
是为了感谢你们每一个人
because I wanted to thank each and every one of you
感谢你们在这里所做的工作
for the work that you're doing here
让你们知道美国在哀悼
and let you know that America mourns.
这
This...
这是疯狂的行为
This was an act of madness.
这是恐怖行为
This was an act of terror.
昨天  我们见到了人性最坏的一面
Yesterday, we saw the worst in humanity.
今天  我见到了最好的一面
Today, I see it's best.
我知道你们都很累  很害怕
I know you're all tired, scared.
我知道你们想知道真相  想知道凶手是谁
I know you want answers, someone to blame,
该找谁算账
someone to fight against.
-你们要知道我也是这么想的  -怎么了
- I need you to know that I want that, too. - What?
虽然现在
And even, though, today,
-看上去我们像是失败了  -密歇根州
- it might look as though we've fallen... - It's Michigan.
我向你们保证我们会再次崛起的
I promise you we will rise again
密歇根州  迪尔伯恩
警察袭击
而且会更好更强大
better and stronger.
我们所失去的
Those who we've lost...
是国家的领导人  亲人
are leaders, family members...
以及我们所爱的人
and loved ones.
我向你们发誓  他们绝不会白白死去
I swear to you, they will not have died in vain.
你看密歇根州怎么了
Hey, you see what's going on in Michigan.
此时此刻我们所在的这个地方
This place where we stand right here, right now...
将永远都是神圣的土地
will forever be hallowed ground,
而且我们必须
and we must always...
永远铭记这里的人们所付出的
respect the incredible sacrifice
伟大牺牲
that was made here.
总统先生  你对发生在迪尔伯恩的
Mr. President, do you have anything to say
警察殴打一名穆斯林青年的事件
about the Muslim teenager in Dearborn
有什么要说的吗
who was beaten by police?
总统现在不接受任何提问
The President's not answering any questions right now.
-谢谢  -没有要回应的吗  柯克曼总统
- Thank you. - You have no response, President Kirkman?
-我没听清问题  -那个被警察
- I-I didn't hear the question. - The Muslim teenager
殴打的穆斯林青年  总统先生
who was beaten by police, Mr. President.
-你有什么要说的吗  -什么
- Do you have a comment? - What?
你是否担心人权正在被侵犯
Are you concerned that their civil rights are being violated?
白宫方面是否担心
Is the White House concerned
对穆斯林群体的暴力会升级
about escalating violence against Muslims?
你会让美国人挨打吗  柯克曼先生
Are you gonna let Americans get beaten, Mr. Kirkman.
把手拿出来
Show me your hands!
-把手拿出来  -我没做错什么  别碰我
- Show me your hands! - I didn't do anything wrong. Don't touch me.
有枪  有枪
Gun! Gun!
掩护  撤离到车上
Cover and evacuate to the car.
别碰他  他什么都没做
Get your hands off him. He's not doing anything.
是部手机  是部手机
It's a phone. It's a phone!
凤凰在我这  重复  凤凰在我这
I have Phoenix! I repeat, I have Phoenix!
后退  后退
Back up! Back up!
后退
I said back up!
走走走
Go, go, go!
马上给我联系罗伊斯州长
Get me Governor Royce on the phone now.
我们一直在联系  他不接电话
We've been trying. He won't take the call.
什么叫他不接电话
What do you mean he won't take the call?
知道那个孩子的情况吗
Do we know anything about the condition of the boy,
密歇根州那个
the one in the Michigan?
他内出血  正在手术
He's in surgery with internal bleeding.
先生  他知道我们在找他  可他不管
He knows we're calling, sir. He doesn't care.
我要跟总检察长办公室的
I want to talk to a couple lawyers
几个律师谈谈
from the Attorney General's Office.
他叫什么
What's his name?
-丹尼·法耶德  夫人  -他多大了
- Danny Fayad, ma'am. - How old is he?
有几个总检察长的候选人可能会帮上忙
We have a couple A.G. candidates who could be helpful.
叫他们过来
Bring them in.
抱歉打扰你  夫人
Sorry to bother you, ma'am.
-你女儿在楼上要找你  -好的
- Your daughter needs you upstairs. - Okay.
汤姆  那个男孩  他17岁
Tom, the boy... he's 17 --
和李奥同岁
The same age as Leo.
佩妮要找我  我得走了
Penny needs me. I got to go.
我不需要跟你解释什么  汉娜
I don't have to explain myself to you Hannah.
我向总统说的是我认为
I gave the President what I determined
最直接相关的情报
was the most relevant intel.
你告诉他的正是这起事件的凶手
Or you gave him what the group who did this
想要你告诉他的
wanted you to give him.
如果他没有掌握全部情况他怎么领导我们
How can he lead if he doesn't have all the facts?
那你把全部情况告诉我啊
Then you should have given them to me.
听我说
Look, it's not...
我不是不相信你  或者不想相信你
that I don't belive you, or that I don't want to.
有人炸掉了国会大厦
Someone blew up the Capitol.
谁知道还会发生什么
Who knows what's possible anymore.
除此之外  现在掌权的人
On top of that, we got a guy in office
是排在继承顺序的第十一位那个
who's number 11 in the line of succession.
我现在不能向他汇报推测出来的事情
I can't go to him with speculation right now.
所以  如果你想让我跟他说你的想法
So, if you want me to go back to him with your theory,
请拿出证据来
please prove it.
密歇根州的情况已经失控了
The situation in Michigan is out of control.
那个青年现在情况很危急
Now we've got a teenager in critical condition.
我想要知道在法律层面我有哪些选择
I need to know what my legal options are right now.
总统先生
Well, Mr. President.
你可以使用最高条款
You can invoke the Supremacy Clause,
发布一条行政命令
issue an executive order
让罗伊斯州长命令他那里的警察停手
saying Governor Royce must force his police to stand down.
这个办法不好
That's a bad call.
发布行政命令会被别人认为很不友好
E.O.S can be perceived as very hostile.
那你有什么建议
Then what would you suggest?
总统宣言
A Presidential Proclamation.
这没有实质意义  只是象征性的行为
Which is nothing more than a symbolic empty gesture.
会让人觉得很软弱  先生
It -- it looks weak, sir.
布什总统在卡特里娜飓风后
Bush used a Proclamation
通过发布总统宣言来保护了灾区的安全
to secure disaster areas after Katrina.
我觉得这可不是个没有实质意义的行为
That hardly seems like an empty gesture to me.
我也不建议把发布戒严令排除在外  先生
I wouldn't take declaring Martial Law off the table either, sir.
如果你想成为
If you want this to be
史上在位最短的总统
the shortest presidency in history.
我就直说了吧
Let me get this straight.
行政命令会被视为敌对恶意
An executive order will be perceived as too hostile,
总统宣言势单力孤
a Presidential Proclamation -- too weak.
戒严令也许非常明智
Martial Law -- either very, very smart
也许具有巨大的自我摧残性
or incredibly self-destructive.
两位  我来问你们一个问题
Guys, let me ask you a question.
你们到底会不会同意我的决定
Can you agree on anything?
-会  -不会
- Yes. - Not really.
好极了
Great.
她怎么样了
How is she?
你认为呢
Well, how do you think she is?
她刚刚看到自己的爸爸差点被人踩死
She just watched her father almost get trampled.
我交给你一个任务
You had one job --
-不让她看电视  -我照做了
- to keep her away from the TV. - I did.
后来你没做到
Until you didn't.
你把她一个人丢在这里
Y-You left her alone.
我有电话要接
I got a phone call.
照看她不是我的责任
It-it's not my job to be her parent.
你猜怎么着
Well, guess what.
今时不同往日了
We're all doing jobs that we weren't doing yesterday.
李奥  我们的生活发生了巨变
Leo, nothing's the same anymore.
我知道这个要求很过分
Look, I know it's asking a lot.
但你得快点成长
But you're just gonna have to grow up faster.
和以前相比  我有更多的事要指望你
I-I'm gonna need to count on you in more ways than ever.
你能做到吗
Can I do that?
能吗
很快就会知道了
Guess we'll find out.
把这些文件带去财政部
Take these to Treasury.
告诉他们我会亲自签署命令
Tell them Social Security checks will keep going out,
-社会保障金会继续发放  -是  长官
- if I have to sign them myself. - Yes, sir.
亚伦  我们不是已经达成共识了吗
Aaron, I thought we were in agreement.
说真的吗  将军
Really, General?
达成什么共识
About what?
他手足无措  力所不及
He's in over his head, out of his depth.
你要说服你的新上司
You need to convince your new boss
阿尔-萨卡就是爆炸事件的罪魁祸首
that Al-Sakar is behind the bombing.
他不是说得很清楚了吗
I think he was pretty clear in there.
在确定之前  他不会乱任命官职的
Until he's certain, he will not name anyone.
我记得  说服他是你的职责
And as I recall, it's your job to convince him.
-亚伦  你是幕僚长  -其实我不是
- Aaron, you're Chief of Staff. - Actually, I'm not.
-那谁才是  -他还没任命
- So, who is? - He hasn't named one, yet.
他又在犹豫不决
And yet another trigger he won't pull.
在看书吗
Light reading?
很可惜  看来维基百科
Well, sadly, it seems that Wikipedia
在宪法理论方面的资料有些单薄
is a little thin on constitutional-law theory.
关于密歇根州事件
Well, did the lawyers
律师团没想出解决办法吗
not give you any answers about Michigan.
他们想出了一堆办法
They gave me plenty of answers.
但是都不适用
They just weren't the right ones.
这不是最重要的
It doesn't even matter, yet.
我没法和罗伊斯州长通电话
I can't get Governor Royce back on the phone.
也许是时候对他采取强硬的态度了
Well, maybe it's time to force his hand.
什么意思
What do you mean?
当年乔治·华莱士拒绝服从
When George Wallace refused an order
合并阿拉巴马州学校的命令
to integrate schools in Alabama,
约翰·肯尼迪让他的兄弟联合国民警卫队
J.F.K. had his brother federalize the National Guard
迫使他遵守法律
and forced him to obey the law.
联合国民警卫队
"Federalize the National Guard."
聪明的点子  但却有些...
Well, it's brilliant, but it's also a little --
太过暴力
Nuclear.
没错
Yeah.
我不需要暴力的解决方案
I don't need a nuclear solution.
我需要用政治手段来解决问题
I need a political one.
好在我们家里有一位政治家
Good thing we have - a politician in the family.
到时再看吧
We'll see about that.
总统先生  一号线有您的电话
Mr. President, your call's on line 1.
我是
Yeah.
好的  非常感谢你
Okay, thank you very much.
汤姆
Tom?
-密歇根州的那个孩子  -丹尼·法亚德
- The boy from Michigan. - Danny Fayad.
刚刚死了
He just died.
总统先生
Mr. President.
-告诉我你找到他了  -是的
- Tell me you got him. - Yes.
罗伊斯州长和霍斯拉滕议员
Governor Royce and Congresswoman Hookstraten
都是美国企业研究所的董事会成员
are both on the board of the American Enterprise Institute.
只有他们能让他回来...
If anyone can get him back to the table...
聪明  做得好
That was smart. Good job.
好了  总统先生
Okay, Mr. President.
他现在回来了
He's coming back on the line now.
-谢谢你  -不客气  长官
- Thank you. - My pleasure, sir.
罗伊斯州长
Governor Royce.
要找到你还真不容易啊
You're a hard man to reach.
我之前和你说过  我很忙
Well, I told you before. I'm pretty busy.
我们会尽力减轻你的工作量
Well, we're gonna try and lighten the load for you,
郑重声明
for the record,
我现在下令  让你手下的警察退下
I am ordering you to have your police stand down
停止侵扰迪尔伯恩的穆斯林社区
and stop harassing the Muslim community in Dearborn.
并且释放
I also need you to release
所有被你们扣押的
everybody that you've picked up today
还没被你正式定罪的民众
that you have not formally charged with a crime.
我告诉过你了
Look, I told you before,
我的警察们在尽其所能
my police are doing what they have to do
保护我的公民们
to protect my citizens.
恕我直言  州长  他们不是您的公民
With all due respect, Governor, they're not your citizens.
他们是我的  我的职责就是保护他们
They're mine, and it's my job to protect them.
你本来就不该有这职责
It's a job you have no business doing.
宪法可不这么说
Well, not according to the Constitution.
州长  你还应该知道
Governor, you should also know
你的警察在不知情情况下
that your police unknowingly picked up
抓了三名为国土安全部
three undercover operatives
进行长期调查任务的
working on a long lead investigation
卧底探员
for Homeland Security.
我不能告诉你他们的名字  因为这是机密
I can't give you their names because it's classified,
而你的安全级别不够
and you don't have clearance.
因此我要你释放
That is why I need you to release
你今天抓的所有人
everybody that you've picked up today.
我不会这么做的
Well... I'm not gonna do that.
那么  州长
Well, then, Governor,
你这是阻碍联邦调查
you'll be obstructing a federal investigation.
你肯定知道这样做的后果
I'm sure you're aware of the consequences for that.
我只是想保证我的人民安全
Look, I'm just trying to keep my people safe.
今早的丹尼·法耶德有多安全
How safe is Danny Fayad this evening?
州长  我现在就要你的回答
Governor, I need your answer now.
我会给州警打电话
I'll call the State Police,
告诉他们解除警备
tell them to stand down
并释放抓到的所有人
and release everyone we've picked up.
谢谢
Thank you.
总统先生  需要我联系国土安全部
Mr. President, would you like me to contact Homeland Security,
通知他们的探员已被释放吗
tell them their agents have been released?
里面没有探员
There were no agents.
那是虚张声势
It was a bluff.
权宜之计  暂时先止止血
A band-aid - to stop the bleeding for now.
好样的  总统先生
Well done, Mr. President.
罗伊斯州长是个好人
Governor Royce is a good man.
他只是今天犯了错
He was just wrong today.
-感谢你的协助  金布尔  -总统先生
- Thank you for your help, Kimble. - Sir.
谢谢大家
Thank you, everyone.
干得好
Great work.
赛斯  你能等一下吗
Seth, can you hold up for a minute?
跟我走走
Walk with me.
特区警察给白宫总机打电话
D.C. Police called the White House switchboard,
要确认你在这里工作
wanted to confirm that you worked here.
今天早晨发生了什么
What happened this morning?
和密歇根发生的事一样
What happened in Michigan.
和一直发生的一样
What always happens.
当人们不知道敌人是谁时
When people don't know who their enemy is,
他们就开始向我这样的人发难
they start with people who look like me.
他们想让我指出阿尔-萨卡
They want me to name Al-Sakar
是爆炸案的始作俑者
as the group behind the bombing.
但联调局不能百分百确认
But the FBI can't confirm with absolute certainty
就是他们做的
that they did it.
所以我什么都不能做
So, I can't do anything.
否则  我就会像罗伊斯州长一样差劲了
Otherwise, I'd be just as bad as Governor Royce.
我们要找到真相
We got to get this right.
我们会的
We will, sir.
-你怎么回家  -什么
- How are you getting home? - Sorry.
你怎么回家
How are you getting home?
我可以让特工处送你
I can have the Secret Service drive you.
不  不必劳烦了
Oh, no. That won't be necessary.
谢谢  总统先生  我没事的
Thank you, Mr. President. I'll be fine.
小心啊  赛斯
Be careful, Seth.
谢谢您  总统先生
Thank you, sir.
晚安
Good night.
怀特
Wyatt!
是  总统先生
Yes, sir.
能给我丹尼·法耶德父母的电话号码吗
Could I please have the number for Danny Fayad's parents?
我想要你们知道  言语无法表达
I need you to know that words could never express
我对你们失去亲人的哀悼
how sorry I am for your loss.
好  先生  晚安
Yes, sir. Goodnight.
柯克曼国会大厦访问成为灾难
麦克
Hey, Mike.
你不会碰巧有
You wouldn't happen to have a baseball cap
一顶棒球帽吧
laying around, would you?
有  总统先生
Yes, sir.
你失去了亲人吗
You lose someone?
是的
Yeah.
我失去了所有人
I lost everyone.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你的工作
Thank you for your service.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
谢谢
Thank you.
托马斯·亚当·柯克曼
住房与城市发展部的部长
住房与城市发展部的部长  托马斯·亚当·柯克曼规划部门前景
谢谢你带我来这里  麦克
Thanks for bringing me here, Mike.
我很荣幸  总统先生
It's an honor, sir.
失踪
这里  找到一名
Hey, over here! We found one!
有幸存者
We got a survivor!
这里有幸存者
We got a survivor over here!